Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II. Regional Coalitions
  - State Charters
    - NOVA, 2003-03-2003-04 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Portland, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Rochester, 2003-12 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - San Antonio, 2003-03 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Southeast Michigan, 2002-10-2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - South Florida, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - St. Joseph Valley Project, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Western Massachusetts, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Rhode Island, 2003-01 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - St. Louis, 2002-11 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Toledo, 2002-11 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Triangle Area, 2004-03 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Tucson, 2003-03 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Utah, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Vermont, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - DC JWJ, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - Columbus, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - Colorado, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - Eastern Massachusetts, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - ESSN, 2003-11 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - Chicago, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - Cleveland, 2002-11 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Long Island Charter, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - Long Island, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 47)
    - Mahoning Valley, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 48)
    - Knoxville, 2002-11 (Box 48, Folder 49)
    - Kentucky, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 50)
    - Mid-Hudson Valley, 2003-12 (Box 48, Folder 51)
    - New Mexico, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 52)
    - Atlanta, 2003-04 (Box 48, Folder 53)
    - Mid-Willamette, 2003-04 (Box 48, Folder 54)
    - Milwaukee, 2003-10 (Box 48, Folder 55)
    - Montana, 2002-10 (Box 48, Folder 56)
    - Nashville, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 57)
    - New York City, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 58)
    - Washington State JWJ, 2002-11 (Box 48, Folder 59)
    - Eugene, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 60)
    - Albany JWJ, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 61)
    - Albany Chapter, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 62)
    - Austin, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 63)
    - Bloomington, 2003-03-21 (Box 48, Folder 64)
    - Buffalo, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - Central Indiana JWJ, 2002-11 (Box 48, Folder 66)
    - Central Oregon JWJ, 2004-03 (Box 48, Folder 67)
- Series III. Workers' Rights Board
  Further material on individual states' Workers' Rights Boards is located in the Regional Coalitions series.
  - WRB, 1994-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Workers' Rights Board, 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Workers' Rights Board Miscellaneous, 1994-2000 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - JWJ Workers' Rights Board Advisory Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Local WRB Case Studies, Clips, and Examples, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - JWJ Workers' Rights Board Stories, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - WRB Advisory Committee - Mailing, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - WRB Conference Call, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - WRB Mailings, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - WRB Testimony in Congressional Record (Chicago AM), 1998-05 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - A.M. Interfaith - Original, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - WRB Success Stories, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Workers Rights Directory, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Workers Rights Directory, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Portland WRB - Teachers Contract, 2000-2011 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Workers' Rights Directory, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cleveland WRB, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Portland Area workers' Rights Boards: Hearing on the Right to Organize, 2001-06-13 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Workers Rights, Communities' Fights: WRBS, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Workers Rights, Communities' Fights: WRBS, 2001-09-09 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Workers Rights Spreadsheets, 2001-10-09 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Contains printed spreadsheet lists of contacts, funders, foundations, and organizations.
  - WRB Recession Hearings, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - DC WRB, 2001-2008 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - WRB Update, Spring 2002 - Fall 2003 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - WRB Update, Fall (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
  - WRB Program (Midwest Gathering), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - WRB Resource Originals (Midwest Gathering), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Midwest WRB Gathering, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - WRB Gathering Logistics, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NC WRB, 2002-08-2003-02 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - WA State WRB, 2002-10-2003-07 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Additional WRB Samples, 2002-2012 (Box 7, Folder 28-30)
  - Workers' Rights Directory, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - WNY Workers' Rights Board Hearing on the Health Care Crisis, 2003-12-04 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - WRB Testimony, 2003-12-10 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - WRB Update, Fall (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - NWRB Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Local WRB Development - Building New Boards, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - St. Louis WRB, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - RI WRB, 2003-2011 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - NWRB Recruitment Correspondences, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Includes signed letter from Noam Chomsky.
  - NWRB Nominations/Lists, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - WRB Media Clips, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Chicago WRB, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Chicago WRB: Walmart, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - WRB Update, Summer (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Angelica, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Packet for WRB Track at S+L Gathering, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Take Back America: Campaign for America's Future Conference Program, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - WRB Track S+L, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Boston WRB, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - National WRB, 2004-07 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - June 2 Hearing, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Angelica Program + Prep, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Angelica Report, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Angelica NWRB, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - NWRB Launch Proposal, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - National Workers' Rights Board Hearing, 2004-06-02 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Including "This is Comcast: Silencing Our Voice at Work" report.
  - Wackenhut, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Comcast, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - WRB Update, Summer (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - WRB Reports, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Quebecor, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Quebecor World Letters, 2004-11 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Quebecor World Letters, 2004-12 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - National WRB Campaigns, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 19-20)
  - National WRB Nomination Forms, Orientations, and Updates, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Knoxville WRB, 2005-04-2005-05 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Mailing: Angelica Report, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Verizon Wireless, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Atlanta WRB, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - National WRB Committee, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Comcast, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - WRB Update, Summer (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - American Red Cross, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Subscriptions, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Administration, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - WRB Workshop Originals - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Campaign for Workers rights, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Walmart, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    two DVDs
  - Misc., 2006 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - NWRB, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - National Campaign Media, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Partnerships, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - WRB Update, Spring (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Workers' Rights Directory, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - Workers' Rights Plenary, 2007-12 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - WA WRB, 2008 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Workers' Rights Directory, 2008 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - St. Louis WRB Cross Train, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Workers Rights Directory, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Making Change at Walmart, 2011-2015 (Box 52, Folder 43-44)
  - NWRB, 2012-2013 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Indianapolis WRB, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Durham/NEX, 2013 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - North Bay WRB, 2014-2015 (Box 52, Folder 48)
- Series IV. SLAP/USSA
  Boxes 14-16 contain the files of organizer Treston Davies-Faulkner.
  - Field Action News, 1999-2006 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - USAS Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers, 1997-11-25 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Labor, NAFTA and APEC, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - SLAP, Day of Action, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - SLAP Day of Action, 2000-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - UFW, Strawberry Campaign, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - GROW, Other Training, Living Wage, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - AT&T Comcast Merger, CWA, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Jobs Loss and Recession Post 9-11, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Health Care Field Work, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Smithfield Blank Sign in Sheets, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Field Action, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Field Notes and Materials, 2002-04 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - April Press Clips, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - General Field Team, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Field Team General, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Floppy Disk Inside Folder
  - Field Team, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Media Tool Kit, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Funding, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Public Welfare Campaign Final Report, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Labor Publications, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Labor Documents, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Spanish and English
  - "World", 2001 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - "World", 2001 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - "World" and Miscellaneous Documents, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Temple University and Public Education, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Drug Policy in Schools, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Jobs with Justice Planning Stuff, SLAP, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - SLAP Presentation Strategy, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Campaigns, SLAP Related, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Jobs with Justice and SLAP Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Jobs with Justice Transition Materials, SLAP, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Rebuilding Bridges, The New Connection Between Students and Labor, 1999-11-12-1999-11-14 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - General Living Wage Information, 2000-2006 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Living Wage Resources, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Talking Points (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Manual Stuff, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sample press Releases, 2005-09-29 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SLAP Press April 4 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Job Application, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Evaluations, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - January 20-22 Evaluations, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - GROW Strategy Chart, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Direct Action Handouts (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Group Dynamics, Consensus, 2006-03-4 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Group Dynamics Questions (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Campus Living Wage Project, 2005-09-01 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - UC San Diego Demands (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - UC San Diego, 2005-04 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Georgetown University Demands, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Georgetown Articles, 2005-03 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Georgetown Policy, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Washington University Survey (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Washington University Case Study, 2005-04 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Harvard and Campus Living Wage, Spring and Summer 2001 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Harvard Living Wage, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - April 4 2002 Materials (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - April 4 2002 Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - April 4 2002 Outreach and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - SLAP Material Requests, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - April 4 2001 Materials (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - April 4 2001 Grid and Numbers (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - April 4 2001 Planning (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - April 4 2001 Organizing Kit (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - A4 2001 Media and Flyers, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - April 4 2000 Materials (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - April 4 2000 Day of Action Media Stuff, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - April 4 Local Reports, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - April 2000 Materials (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Jobs with Justice USSA Materials, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Highlights April 4 2000 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Day of Action Media Kit, Organizing Kit and Grid, D10 1997 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - USSA Strategic Planning, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - USSA Manual, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - General Materials (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - General Workshop Evaluation, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Highlander Training, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - United Council's Building Unity Conference (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - United Council's Annual Building Unity Conference, 2001-11-16-2001-11-18 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Student-Labor Roundtable Agenda and Sign-In Sheet, 2001-10-24 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - USSA Transition Materials, SLAP, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Memos and Emails, SLAP, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Southern Anti-Racism Network (SARN), 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - People's Weekly "World" (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Political Activism Documents, 1999-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - USSA Legislative Conference 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - USSA Board of Directors Meeting in San Diego, 2001-01 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Chicago JWJ, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - National Student Congress, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Treston Faulkner's Congress 2G Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - USSA News, 2002-03-13 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Workshop Outlines (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Workshop Originals, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Manual (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Contains two CD's
  - Anti-Oppression Resources, 2004-10-06 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Anti-Oppression Resources (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 55th National Student Congress, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Student-Labor Roundtable Materials, 2001-10-24 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Student Labor Pre-Conference, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Student Labor Pre-Conference 2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Student Labor Pre-Conference 1999 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Notes, SEJAC 2009 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Communication with Major Gregory, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Workshop and Useful Rules, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Travel, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Local Students Contacts and Lists (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Grow" News, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - General "Grow" Documents, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Student-Labor GROW Originals, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NSLA GROW, 2000-11-02-2000-11-05 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - New GROW Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Labor GROW, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - GROW Strategy Charts, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - GROW 2001 Evaluations (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Complete NSLA GROW Packet, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Useful Professional Development Worksheets, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Local SIAP Development, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Strategic Planning, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Anti-Oppression Articles, 2004-10-06 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - SLAP Presentations to JWJ Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - General Documents (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - 2001 SLACtivist news (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Worker Quotes (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - GROW and SLAP Monthly Reports, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - List of Useful Acronyms (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Useful Spanish Words and Phrases (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - ARAW Article 2, 2004-12-14 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - ARAW Articles, 2005-02-24 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Campaign Filled Out GROW (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - SLAP Internal Documents, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - SLAP Hiring, 2002-04 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Reimbursement and Check Request Copies, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Student-Worker Workshop Handouts (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Direct Action handouts (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Reimbursements and Receipts, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Credit Card Statement Copies, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - CC Receipts Originals, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Credit Card Receipts, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Staff meeting Notes and Materials, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Staff Meeting Notes and Materials, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Fast Track 2001 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - USSA 53rd Annual National Student Congress, 2000-06-30-2000-08-6 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Agents of Change, 1996-1999 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Student Activism News, 1997-2008 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Student Labor Action, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Sweat-Free Campus Campaign: Organizer's Manual, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
  - Graduate Student-Employee Lists, 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - The Center for Campus Organizing, 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - SLAP Bios, MOU, Organizing Approach, 1999-2001 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Earlham College Fair Wage Report, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - April 4th - Day of Action - SLAP, 2000-03 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - April 4th, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - SLAP + Nat'l Student - Labor Day of Action, 2000-04-04-2001-04-04 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - United States Student Association, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Prison Moratorium Project, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Campus Campaigns + Events, Fall 2000 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Day of Action Coordinators List, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Creation of SLAP, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Campus Worker Manual, 2001-04 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - USSA Campus Info. and Misc., 2001 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - SLACtivist, Summer/Fall 2001 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - SLAP Field Priorities, Fall 2001 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - A4 - local action materials, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - SLAP Day of Action 4 pager, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - SLAP Day of Action 2001 Highlights (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Act Up! Fight Back! Materials, Spring 2001 - Fall 2002 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - New Era, Spring 2001 - Summer 2002 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - SEIU, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - USSA founding + misc, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Student Organizing Toolkits, 2001-2004 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Living Wage Action Coalition Grant Reporting, 2001-2006 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - SLAP Misc., 2001-2008 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2001-2010 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Misc., 2001-2012 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - GROW Handouts, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Campus Living Wage Manual, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 35-36)
  - 2002 SLAP Day of Action 4-pager (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - SLAP Day of Action 2002 Highlights (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - April 4th, 2002, 2002-04-04 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - April 4, 2002 Press Clips, 2002-04-04 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - SLACtivist, Fall/Winter 2002 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - SLACtivist, Winter/Spring 2002 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Carl Lipscombe, 2002-2004 (Box 49, Folder 43-44)
  - Young Workers Project, 2002-2005 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - USAS Materials, 2002-2005 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - 2003 SLAP Week of Action 4-pager (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - USSA Congress + SLAP Materials, 2014-2015 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - SLAP Goals, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Amass Corporatization Pamphlet "Beating the Barcode", 2004 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 2004 SLAP Week of Action 4-pager (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - SLAP Week of Action Clips, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Slap Week of Action 2004 Highlights (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - SLACtivist, Fall 2004 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - SLACtivist, Winter/Spring 2004 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Student Organizing, 2004-2008 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - The Campus Living Wage Project, 2005-07-18 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Jobs with Justice Binder, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
  - Campus Organizing Manual, Summer 2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Living Wage Action Coalition Proposals, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Ontario Skills Development Symposium, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - SLAP Transition Binder, 2006-06 (Box 50, Folder 18-19)
  - USSA National Student Congress, 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 20-21)
  - Verizon Campus Organizing Kit, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - USSA Meeting, Maria Escobar, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - SLAP, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - SLAP Week of Action Reports, 2008-2010 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Week of Action Planning, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - SLAP Planning, 2009-08 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Leg Con, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - USSA, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Maria-Chris Transition, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Student Unionism, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - USSA National Student Congress, 2011-2013 (Box 50, Folder 31-32)
  - Transition, 2012 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - USSA Electoral Action Training, 2012-06-12-2012-06-13 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - SLAP/USSA Fact Sheets + Flyers, 2012-2015 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - National Student Power Conference, 2013 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Sallie Mae, 2013 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Student Debt Alignment Retreat, 2013 (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Series V. American Rights At Work (ARAW)
  - ARAW Press Clips, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - ARAW Press Clips, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
  - ARAW Press Clips, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - ARAW Press Clips, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - ARAW Press Clips, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 7-8)
  - Press Clips, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Press Clips, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 10-11)
  - Press Clips, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
  - Press Clips, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 14-15)
  - Press Clips, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 16-18)
  - Press Clips, 2008-2013 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - The Labor Day List, 2005-2010 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Award Celebrations, 2005-2015 (Box 42, Folder 21-22)
  - Walking the Walk: Allies in Action Supporting Workers, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Beyond the Weekend, 2011-2012 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - AWAR Folder, Undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Workers' Rights Monitor, 2004-08 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - FedUp With FedEx, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Socially Responsible Business Program: Cingular Wireless, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - No Bargain: Comcast and the Future of Workers' Rights, 2004-06 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Material, 2003-2013 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Statements on Labor Law, Union, Economy, and Democracy, 2005-2009 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Fact Over Fiction: Opposition to Card Check Doesn't Add up, 2006-03 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Partnerships In Education: How Labor Management Collaboration is Transforming Public Schools, 2011-05 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Broken Promises: Verizon Neglects its Commitment to Provide Good Jobs and Quality Service, 2007-09 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Everybody's Got a Right!, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Forging a New Labor Policy For 21st Century: An American Rights at Work Conference at Harvard University, 2006-12-01-2006-12-02 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Two Movements, One Goal: The NAACP and Organized Labor, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Sierra Club, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Where Do You Stand?: Stories from an American Mill, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Fighting for a Voice: Walmart Workers Speak Out Despite Systematic Labor Abuse, 2013-05 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Employee Free Choice Act, 2005-2011 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Lowering the Bar or Setting the Standard?: Deutsche Telekom's U.S. Labor Practices, 2009-12 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    English and German
  - American Rights At Work, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - ICED OUT: How Immigration Enforcement Has Interfered With Worker's Rights, 2009-09 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Publications - Fact Sheets, Eye on the NLRB, Talking Points, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Improving Government Through Labor-Management Collaboration and Employee Ingenuity, 2014-01 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Wal-Mart: Rolling Back Workers' Wages, Rights, and The American Dream, 2005-11 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Some of Them are Brave: The Unfilled Promise of American Labor Law, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Free and Fair?: How Labor Law Fails U.S. Democratic Election Standard, 2005-06 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Neither Free Nor Fair: The Subversion of Democracy Under National Labor Relations Board Elections, 2007-07 (Box 45, Folder 10)